ebicycles.com 2018-02-28

# Website Privacy Statement

## ACKNOWLEDGEMENT AND ACCEPTANCE OF TERMS

eBicycles is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Statement sets forth our current privacy practices with regard to the information we collect when you or your computer interact with our website. By accessing eBicycles, you acknowledge and fully understand eBicycles’s Privacy Statement and freely consent to the information collection and use practices described in this Website Privacy Statement.

## PARTICIPATING MERCHANT POLICIES

Related services and offerings with links from this website, including vendor sites, have their own privacy statements that can be viewed by clicking on the corresponding links within each respective website. Online merchants and others who participate in eBicycles services are encouraged to participate in industry privacy initiatives and to take a responsible attitude towards consumer privacy. However, since we do not have direct control over the policies or practices of participating merchants and other third parties, we are not responsible for the privacy practices or contents of those sites. We recommend and encourage that you always review the privacy policies of merchants and other third parties before you provide any personal information or complete any transaction with such parties.

## INFORMATION WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT

eBicycles collects certain information from and about its users three ways: directly from our Web Server logs, the user, and with Cookies.

## Web Server Logs

When you visit our Website, we may track information to administer the site and analyze its usage. Examples of information we may track include:

  * Your Internet protocol address.
  * The kind of browser or computer you use.
  * Number of links you click within the site.
  * State or country from which you accessed the site.
  * Date and time of your visit.
  * Name of your Internet service provider.
  * Web page you linked to our site from.
  * Pages you viewed on the site.

## Use of Cookies

eBicycles may use cookies to personalize or enhance your user experience. A cookie is a small text file that is placed on your hard disk by a Web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a Web Server in the domain that issued the cookie to you.

Cookies allow websites to have features that make web browsing easier. For example, a site may allow you to personalize a web page, navigate within a site, save preferences and/or retain login information between visits.

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies. If you reject cookies by changing your browser settings then be aware that this may disable some of the functionality on our Website.

## Advertising

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, [click here](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

## Personal User Information

Visitors to our website can register to purchase services. When you register, we will request some personal information such as name, address, email, telephone number or fax number, account number and other relevant information. If you are purchasing a service, we will request financial information. Any financial information we collect is used only to bill you for the services you purchased. For other types of registrations, we will ask for the relevant information. You may also be asked to disclose personal information to us so that we can provide assistance and information to you. For example, such data may be warranted in order to provide online technical support and troubleshooting.

We will not disclose personally identifiable information we collect from you to third parties without your permission except to the extent necessary, including:

  * To fulfill your service requests for services.
  * To protect ourselves from liability,
  * To respond to legal process or comply with law, or
  * In connection with a merger, acquisition, or liquidation of the company.

## USE OF WEB BEACONS OR GIF FILES

eBicycles Web pages may contain tiny images known as Web beacons – sometimes also called single-pixel gifs – that allow eBicycles to count users who have visited those pages and to deliver co-branded services. We may include Web beacons in promotional e-mail messages or newsletters in order to determine whether messages have been opened and acted upon.

Some of these Web beacons may be placed by third party service providers to help determine the effectiveness of our advertising campaigns or email communications. These Web beacons may be used by these service providers to place a persistent cookie on your computer. This allows the service provider to recognize your computer each time you visit certain pages or emails and compile anonymous information in relation to those page views, which in turn enables us and our service providers to learn which advertisements and emails bring you to our website and how you use the site. eBicycles prohibits Web beacons from being used to collect or access your personal information.

## ACCESSING WEB ACCOUNT INFORMATION

We will provide you with the means to ensure that personally identifiable information in your web account file is correct and current. You may review this information by logging into your account with your e-mail address and password.

## CHANGES TO THIS STATEMENT

eBicycles has the discretion to occasionally update this privacy statement. When we do, we will also revise the _updated_ date at the top of this Privacy page. We encourage you to periodically review this privacy statement to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. Your continued use of the service constitutes your agreement to this privacy statement and any updates.

## CONTACTING US

If you have questions regarding our Privacy Statement, its implementation, failure to adhere to this Privacy Statement and/or our general practices, please contact us at info@eBicycles or send your comments to:

**eBicycles.com**  
Dear Mango, LLC  
Attention: Privacy Statement Personnel  
11 Palatine Road  
Califon, NJ 07830

eBicycles will use commercially reasonable efforts to promptly respond and resolve any problem or question.
